[OVERDO]
[Episode 27]
Here they come. The newlyweds are here.
How nice.
Come here.
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Who is this?
Who is this person?
Let me go!
His fiancée?
For this first dance,
dance with me.
-Where's Le'an?
-What's going on?
Don't worry.
He's perfectly safe.
Ye Zhihong is the woman Qingyu loves.
So what?
What right do you have to question me?
Or
are you just jealous?
♪ In those fleeting
three seconds of twilight ♪
You're simply impossible to reason with.
♪ An amber dream shimmers
within the glass ♪
♪ The ice of loneliness
melts away in the warmth ♪
I've showed up as promised
and witnessed your absurd wedding.
♪ Your evasive gaze
gives your heart away ♪
Can I take Le'an away with me now?
♪ Don't tell me ♪
Thank you all
for attending our wedding today.
♪ You're tired again; this time, don't ♪
The one beside me
♪ Don't push me away
only to draw me close ♪
is the one I'm going to marry.
♪ Why so nervous? ♪
W-What's this about?
What's going on?
♪ Please don't stay frozen for too long ♪
Isn't that his elder brother's
former fiancée?
♪ Say my name ♪
Exactly.
Although the dead
cannot be brought back to life,
♪ Please don't stop ♪
it's still quite rare for someone
to marry his own sister-in-law.
♪ Forgive me, I've loved you for ages ♪
-Exactly.
-Yeah.
That's just too undignified.
♪ Please lull me into absolute surrender ♪
♪ Before you cage me
in a prison of your design ♪
The times are turbulent.
♪ Stop bowing to the crowd ♪
So we'll keep everything simple.
Miss Fang will come visit you again
tomorrow.
♪ Conquer to be free ♪
Just give it to her then.
If you wait any longer,
I'm afraid you'll rub the surface off.
♪ Even if I'm unrepentantly obsessed ♪
♪ I'll let the wrongs just carry on ♪
What do you know?
A ring is a precious item.
Of course I have to
pick a good day to give it to her.
♪ Drunk and unawakened,
waves rage stronger ♪
♪ Let them rage, let them rise ♪
♪ Drench me through ♪
♪ No matter how many words I got wrong,
in the end ♪
♪ I never had what I longed for ♪
♪ Only a receding tide ♪
♪ Just you and me, all else fades away ♪
Consider today our wedding.
But I heard
this woman has a 6-year-old child.
Really?
Absurd.
Mother!
Laiyi.
Take her to see Le'an.
Don't leave!
What a mess.
Exactly.
Whoever acknowledges this marriage
is making an enemy of our Murong family!
Murong Qingyi!
So this is the wedding banquet
you invited me to?
Do you want our Murong family
to become the laughingstock
of all of Nancheng?
She was Qingyu's fiancée.
You...
How could you touch her?
I've told you time and again
that she's not Fang Mulan.
She's Ren Susu.
She always has been.
I don't care
whether her surname is Fang or Ren.
She was Qingyu's fiancée.
She was the one
who was betrothed to Qingyu,
the one who performed
the hair-binding ceremony with him,
and in the end,
the one who observed the funeral rites
for him.
You must never
touch this woman in your life!
The one who was engaged to Qingyu
was Fang Mulan.
Fang Mulan wasn't the only one
who observed the funeral rites for Qingyu.
And the hair-binding ceremony?
The one who performed that ceremony
with her back then
was me.
♪ Forgive me, I've loved you for ages ♪
♪ Please lull me into absolute surrender ♪
♪ Before you cage me
in a prison of your design ♪
You bastard.
♪ Stop bowing to the crowd ♪
They said
she has a son.
♪ Conquer to be free ♪
Whose child
♪ Even if I'm unrepentantly obsessed ♪
is he, exactly?
♪ I'll let the wrongs just carry on ♪
Tell me!
Whose else could it be?
♪ Drunk and unawakened,
waves rage stronger ♪
Mother...
Murong Qingyi.
♪ Surging in, pushing out ♪
If you insist on marrying her,
♪ Drench me through ♪
then from this day onward,
♪ Say it out loud that you own me ♪
you're no longer a member
of the Murong family!
Besides her,
is there anyone else here
who opposes this marriage?
-Congratulations, Principal.
♪ It's so turbulent
I'm afraid I'll get drunk ♪
-Congratulations, Principal.
♪ If I have a dream, let me get drunk ♪
Congratulations, Young Marshal Murong.
♪ It's so turbulent
I'm afraid it'll shatter ♪
Congratulations, Principal.
Congratulations, Young Marshal Murong.
♪ It shatters at the slightest touch ♪
♪ Bittersweet ♪
Congratulations, Principal.
Mother.
Look at these people.
♪ I beg you, don't let me ♪
Do they even have any respect left
for our Murong family?
♪ Suffer this endless pain ♪
♪ No matter how many words I got wrong,
in the end ♪
Let's go.
♪ I never had what I longed for ♪
♪ Only a receding tide ♪
♪ Just you and me, all else fades away ♪
Go investigate this child's background.
We have to get to the bottom of this.
Okay. Got it.
[Lanxin Theater]
Murong Qingyi.
I have something to say to you.
Give me an explanation.
Le'an needs a father.
He needs a complete family.
Is that enough?
So you're using Le'an
to force me to marry you?
Did you even ask what we think?
You're still just as stubborn as ever,
always making decisions on your own.
But you must promise me one thing.
Once I've made up my mind,
I'll ask you to do something for me,
and you must not refuse.
I swear to heaven.
You promised me
that I could ask you to do one thing.
This marriage—
you must accept it.
I accept it. And then what?
Make Le'an accept you as his father,
and then we live happily as a family?
Why not?
If Li Boze could take care of both of you,
then why can't I?
I'm Le'an's father, after all.
How do you expect Le'an to accept
a father who's been gone for 6 years?
If you never tell Le'an I'm his father,
how do you know
he won't be able to accept it?
Ren Susu.
Do you really hate me that much?
You were the one who said you hated me,
that you wished you had never met me.
Given the state of our relationship,
how do you expect me to tell him?
I hate you?
I just refused to give up.
I refused to give up
that tiny bit of hope of
living like a human being.
But now I understand.
Ren Susu,
I hate you.
Fine.
Then from now on,
let's just be a married couple
who hate each other.
Ren Susu, listen.
Le'an is innocent.
Even if it's just an act,
we still have to make it look like
a complete family.
I won't accept that.
You must go through with this marriage!
Let go of me!
Mom.
Let go.
Uncle.
What are you two doing?
Le'an.
I'm not your uncle.
I'm your father.
Mom,
is what he said true?
Are you really my father?
Yes,
I am your father.
This is great.
I finally have a father.
Papa, Mama!
Come out quickly!
Susu!
Fire! Come and help put it out!
Come help put out the fire!
I lost my family,
and he never had a family.
But at this moment,
do we have a chance
to give Le'an a complete family?
How about we go take a family photo?
Mom makes the call.
Mom, Mom.
Can we go take a family photo?
Alright, look here.
Smile.
[Chairman, East Asia Chamber of Commerce]
This...
Is this the drug
that will be sent to Nancheng tomorrow?
Only in its original potency
can it achieve this effect.
The ones sent to Nancheng
will be diluted tenfold,
so the onset of symptoms
and the rate of transmission
will be much slower.
Last time,
you tried to use Fang Youshen's cargo ship
to smuggle the Red Pills
containing the active ingredient,
yet in the end,
all the pills
were destroyed by Fang Youshen.
If this attempt in Nancheng
fails again,
you and your family...
Mr. Zhang.
I know
what you value most is family honor.
If
this batch of drugs is used effectively,
your Zhang family
will be credited with a major achievement.
[Nancheng Station]
[Times Newspaper]
Tao.
Are you sure
you saw it clearly?
Absolutely.
It was the same kind of train
we saw last time.
The cargo that was unloaded
should now be
in the warehouse
at the train station
where the Ying Army is stationed.
That train station is heavily guarded.
How are we supposed to get in?
That's where your expertise comes in.
It's time to go to the train station
to cheer on the troops.
Bravo!
Here it is.
What's going on?
Exactly.
What's this about?
Why did they stop performing?
They were performing just fine.
Exactly.
Where are they?
-Where are they?
-They're gone.
Where did they go?
That's really impressive!
Impressive.
Look. Look over there.
Bravo!
Bravo! Amazing!
-Bravo!
[Confirmed the Zhang family sent someone
to the station. Tracking continues.]
As expected,
the Zhang family sent someone
to the train station.
Send someone to keep an eye
on the train station.
If there's any movement,
report to me immediately.
Got it.
By the way,
Lanxin Theater went to the train station
to cheer on the troops.
What?
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Wasn't it because
you acted like you had a short fuse
the day after the wedding,
forbidding me from mentioning
Miss Ren's name in front of you-
This concerns the Red Pill case.
And you still have the nerve
to banter with me about this?
Go to the training ground
and do 10 laps of frog jumps.
-But I have to go to the train station...
-Just do as I say.
I'll go to the train station myself.
Who's there?
Where's the lock on the door?
Why is it missing?
Who's there?
Come with me.
Why are you here?
No time to explain. Let's go.
Ladies and gentlemen,
how did you like "The Jinshan Temple"
just now?
Bravo! Perform another one!
In that case,
we'll perform
another piece for you all—
"The Crossroads."
Great!
Without the invitation of the Ying Army,
Boss Hai,
what kind of "cheering on the troops"
is this?
Where is Ren Susu?
Right backstage.
Would you like to see
the Young Marshal's magic tricks?
Yes!
Young Marshal!
Wait, wait. No need to panic.
This is part of the show.
Bravo!
Young Marshal, you just couldn't bear
to part with me, could you?
That you had to drag me
into this crappy box with you?
Good thing I was on my guard.
Otherwise, you would've locked me up
in here all by myself.
Since you're already in here,
you might as well
open this crappy box right away.
The box is broken.
We can't get out.
What exactly are you guys up to?
Doing what we're supposed to do.
Unlike certain people
who can't tell right from wrong,
cover things up and turn a blind eye—
a disgrace to the title of
Chief Inspector of Nancheng.
And what about you?
What gives you the right to judge
good and evil?
But at least we dare to pursue the truth.
Do you?
Have you ever done that?
What's the rush?
Does being around me
really bother you that much?
Young Marshal!
What happened?
It seems whether I live or die
depends entirely on what you say,
Young Marshal.
Tell them to open the box.
Charge me with whatever crime you like
and throw me in jail.
That way, I won't be able to
go against you anymore.
Young Marshal!
Are you okay?
I'll pry the box open right away!
No need.
I'm fine.
After that incident,
today's the first time
you've spoken to me,
♪ If the sparks ♪
♪ Could fly back into the gun's muzzle ♪
and yet it's still because
you want to use me.
♪ If I had turned away
when love first bloomed ♪
You're just taking advantage of the fact
that I like you, aren't you?
♪ My true heart hides in the shadows,
left to fate's mercy ♪
Now that you've gotten what you wanted,
♪ Resisting the pull of every temptation ♪
it's time for me to take back what I want.
♪ Hate is the smoke left by dying flames ♪
♪ Behind remains
the bitterness of unspoken feelings ♪
♪ The heart races with every thought ♪
♪ As long as we loved each other,
I don't care ♪
♪ If it's a blessing or a curse ♪
Without a plan—do you want to die?
What are you doing here?
You're my wife.
You're out in the middle of the night.
As your husband, don't I have the right
to ask about it?
-Get them!
-Halt!
Stop!
This way!
Catch them!
That way.
Who's there?
Stop!
-Stop!
-Hurry!
Stop!
Catch them!
Over here.
Careful.
Ren Susu,
you go first.
What about you?
Hurry! Don't let them get away!
Don't worry.
With my status,
they won't dare to touch me.
Just go.
Just pretend
you never knew me.
Go!
♪ Sharper pain, deeper mark ♪
♪ Deeper care, greater torment ♪
Let's go.
♪ I won't give up on you ♪
♪ Don't let go of me ♪
Can you just give me one second,
and love me for that one second?
♪ In exchange for my everything ♪
♪ Will you finally be mine? ♪
♪ Give me love and hate ♪
Qingyi!
♪ I can't break free, I can't escape ♪
♪ This, too, can be called
a lifetime together ♪
♪ We ♪
♪ Remain bound by fate until the end ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
Can you give me just one second...
I told you
I'd be fine.
Le'an finally has a father.
I found this.
The ship on which Godfather met his end
had always
been transporting military supplies
for Li Rongzhang,
but these Red Pills were found mixed in.
Strangely,
the Red Pills on that ship
could cause some terrible illnesses.
After Godfather learned about this,
he set off the explosives on the ship
and sank together with it.
He most likely did so to prevent
that shipment of Red Pills
from falling into the hands of
the general public in Nanyang,
where they would've caused
immeasurable harm.
Back then, I seized a batch of Red Pills
on the southwestern front,
and that was when I began
secretly investigating Li Rongzhang.
The transport route for the Red Pills
necessarily run along
the North-South Railway,
and the tracks and stations along the way
are all controlled by the Ying Army.
Li Rongzhang's only responsible for
transportation.
He doesn't have the skills
to manufacture the pills.
Then who does?
The Zhang family?
Very likely.
On the surface, the Zhang family
runs the gangs in Nancheng,
but they've always been able
to go toe-to-toe with
the warlords and the police.
They must have
overseas backing behind them.
That's just our speculation.
Looks like
we'll have to start investigating
from the source of the drugs.
What's wrong?
Are you hurt?
It's a chronic condition.
What chronic condition?
How come I didn't know
you had an ear condition?
I'm tired.
When we get to the outskirts of Hangcheng,
I'll ask someone to come and pick us up.
Okay.
[Nancheng Station]
Someone broke in last night.
We failed to catch them,
but in the hidden compartment of the box,
we found this.
That bastard Zhang Mingshu.
He actually dared to scheme against me.
Drugs.
You actually dared to mix them
into military supplies.
Look at what your Zhang family has done.
Mr. Li.
How could this be
our Zhang family's doing?
This is clearly your doing.
Over the past few years,
the North-South Railway
has served as a protective network
for transporting Red Pills.
The fact that Red Pills
have spread across the country,
bringing in a steady stream of profits—
that's all thanks to you.
You actually dared to use me.
Aren't you worried I'll blow this open?
Mr. Li.
You've certainly taken quite a cut
from the North–South Railway's
transportation business.
Every gun and every bullet in your army
was paid for with the profits we made
from selling Red Pills.
Isn't it also the Red Pills
that allow you to keep the Murong family
in check right now?
This...
This is no drug.
This is your military funding,
your guns and cannons,
as well as your food, clothing,
and daily necessities.
If this gets out,
you won't be able to keep your position
as Governor of the North-South Railway.
Let's see if the Ying Army
can withstand the wrath
of all of Nancheng,
or even the entire nation.
In the end,
I really can't say
who'll go down first.
Besides,
as for the pharmaceutical factory,
our Zhang family only holds a tiny stake.
The real owners
are in the concession.
You don't need me to remind you
who's behind
the East Asia Chamber of Commerce, do you?
Not to mention you, a mere Governor,
even the government
wouldn't dare confront them head-on.
If you really go all out
and ruin everything,
you'll end up with nothing in the end,
and you won't be able to
walk away unscathed either.
But if you choose to cooperate
for mutual benefit,
what it can bring you is far greater.
This son of yours
is even more ruthless than you.
Your whole family are thugs who go around
wielding sticks and picking fights,
yet just because
you're wearing silk robes now,
you think you can sit at the table
with the big players,
playing games of power and strategy?
What a joke.
Let me tell you this:
I, Li Rongzhang,
am not afraid of going down with you.
Even if it costs me my life,
I'll make sure your Zhang family
goes down with me.
Ren Susu's ear was injured.
Find out exactly what happened.
Get in.
Since you don't want to see me,
this is the only way I can see you.
Just say what you came to say.
You can take a horse to the water
but you cannot make it drink.
You shouldn't have married Ren Susu,
and you especially shouldn't
have made it public.
Whether a horse will drink or not,
you won't know
until you take it to the water.
Anyway, Ren Le'an
is my son.
So you found out after all.
From now on, stop pretending
to be a loving father in front of my son.
If you really want to be a father,
go have a child of your own.
By the way,
now that you know Li Rongzhang
was involved in drug trafficking,
are you going to take any action?
That batch of drugs
has always been supplied by
the Zhang family's pharmaceutical factory
and transported via
the North-South Railway.
But the things hidden among the shipments
may not necessarily
have been known to my father.
Now that he knows,
what does he plan to do?
This is the sample of this batch.
A preliminary inspection
shows something's off.
They're not quite the same
as the ones that have circulated before.
Go seal up the warehouse
and impound these.
Under no circumstances can we
let them enter the market.
So you want me
to investigate my own father?
What?
You don't dare to investigate him?
Even if you don't,
someone else will.
It'll be even harder
to clean up the mess then.
My father did raise us
for more than 10 years, after all.
♪ The more passionate ♪
♪ Our past embrace ♪
When did the upright and honorable
Inspector Li
♪ The more icy ♪
lose his sense of right and wrong?
♪ Our present clash ♪
Or
is your sense of justice
♪ If not tangled in love ♪
conditional to begin with?
♪ We are locked in hate ♪
♪ There is no escaping it ♪
Qingyu once said
that it was because of you and me
that the Murong and Li families
share such a deep bond.
So we're supposed to be
as close as one family.
As close as one family?
♪ Sharper pain, deeper mark ♪
When the nest is destroyed,
no egg can remain intact.
♪ Deeper care, greater torment ♪
Li Boze,
do you really think you can call the shots
for the Murong and Li families?
♪ I won't give up on you ♪
♪ Don't let go of me ♪
♪ Let the ropes of fate ♪
You've been playing the loyal lapdog
out there every day,
♪ Bind you and me ♪
to the point that you've abandoned
even the most basic principles
of truth and justice?
♪ Even if led to a precipice ♪
♪ Together, we fall ♪
Don't you love to bring up Qingyu
all the time?
Then go to his grave
and take a close look at
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
what's inscribed on his tombstone.
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
♪ I can't break free, I can't escape ♪
♪ This, too, can be called
a lifetime together ♪
Fine.
♪ We ♪
If you won't investigate,
♪ Remain bound by fate until the end ♪
I'll do it for you.
♪ Forevermore ♪